Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

SUBHRA PANDA (1) Featured

Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Performance Tuning, Database Administration, System Analysis, Software Troubleshooting, System Analysis, SQL Server.POWER Bi



Current Designation: Consultant - IT

Current Company: Capgemini

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Consultant, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Web

Development, Requirement Gathering, Performance Tuning, Database Administration, System Analysis, Software

Troubleshooting, System Analysis, SQL Server, POWER Bi

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Having around 3.10 years of exp. in Development.

Good knowledge and technically proficient in SQL.

Experience in writing SQL queries by using various joins and sub queries, creating global and local temporary tables, improving performance creating clustered and non-clustered index.

Have sound Knowledge on Schema design according to requirement.

Having experience on Writing MS-SQL and T-SQL scripts such as stored procedures, index planning, query planning based on schema design and problem statement, USER DEFINED FUNCTIONS, Triggers etc.

Providing support in creating, monitoring and troubleshooting the scheduled jobs in SQL SERVER.

Excellent communication, organizational and interpersonal skills.

Optimized database systems for performance efficiency.

Proficient in implementing all transformations available on the SSIS toolbox.

Having very good knowledge on creating, deploying and Scheduling of SSIS packages in SQL Server.

Work Experience

Capgemini as Consultant - IT

Apr 2019 to Till Date

Project Name: AXA_MIS_GULF Client Name: AXA, DUBAI (UAE)

Period MAY 2019 to SEPTMBER 2019

AXA_GULF is one of the global insurance company, offering a wide range of insurance products for corporate as well as for individual customers. AXA_GULF is one of the largest international player in GCC, covering countries like UAE, OMAN, QATAR.

Role Developer

Responsibility Working as a MSBI developer.

Knowledge about database design according to requirement.

Writing SQL queries.

Working on all transformations available on the SSIS toolbox.

Working on creating, deploying and Scheduling of SSIS packages in SQL Server.

Improve performance in optimization.

Providing support in creating, monitoring and troubleshooting the scheduled jobs in SQL SERVER.

Improve performance in optimization.

Working on Performance Tuning in SSIS packages by using Row Transformation, blocking and partial blocking Transformation.

Solution Environment MS-SQL SERVER (2019)

MS-SQL,T-SQL,SSIS Tools

Proiect Name: Baloise

Client Name: Baloise, Belgium.

OCTOBER 2019 to MAY 2020 Period

Baloise Belgium NV provides insurance services. The Company offers a range of insurance solutions for life, family welfare, home, vehicle, savings, liability, accidents, pension plans, businesses, transport, and maritime. Baloise Belgium conducts business in Belgium.

Developer

Working as a MSBI developer. Responsibility

Designing databases and ensuring their stability, reliability and performance.

Working on all transformations available on the SSIS toolbox

Working on creating, deploying and Scheduling of SSIS packages in SQL Server.

Knowledge about database design according to Requirement

Working on Performance Tuning in SSIS packages by using Row Transformation, blocking and partial blocking

Transformation

Design, create and improved database based on users? requirement.

Create of databases according to request.

Improve performance in optimization.

Take regular database update.

Test database and perform bug fixes.

Develop best practice for database design and development activity.

Solution Environment MS-SQL SERVER (2019)

MS-SQL,T-SQL,SSIS Tools Project Name: Unilever

Client Name: Unilever, London, England

JUNE 2020 to Till Date Period

Unilever is a British-Dutch multinational consumer goods company, headquartered in London, England. Its products include food, candy, energy drink, baby food, soft drink, ice cream, tea, cleaning agents, coffee, pet food, chewing gum, juice, beauty products, personal care, breakfast cereals, medicine & healthcare products. Unilever is the largest producer of soap in the world. Unilever is one of the oldest multinational companies and its products are available in around 190 countries

Role Developer

Responsibility Working as a MSBI developer.

Designing databases and ensuring their stability, reliability and performance.

Working on all transformations available on the SSIS toolbox

Working on creating, deploying and Scheduling of SSIS packages in SQL Server.

Knowledge about database design according to Requirement.

Working on Performance Tuning in SSIS packages by using Row Transformation, blocking and partial blocking

Transformation

Design, create and improved database based on users? requirement.

Create of databases according to request.

Improve performance in optimization.

Take regular database update.

Test database and perform bug fixes.

Develop best practice for database design and development activity.

Setting business requirements for BI tools.

Leading BI software development, deployment, and maintenance.

Report curtain and data modeling.

Participation in data warehouse design.

Creating technical documentation for BI tools.

MS-SQL SERVER (2012), VISUAL STUDIO (2019), POWER BI, SSRS Solution Environment

MS-SQL SEVER, VISUAL STUDIO, POWER BI, SSIS

Wipro Technology

Nov 2016 to Apr 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Biju Pattnaik University of Technology in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
SQL ,T-SQL ,SSIS,POWER BI,SSRS	
Ms-Sql server (2012,2017,2019)	
VISUAL STUDIO (2019),MS-POWER BI	
SSRS	
SQL Server AGENT	

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time